What'll it be now, Mr. Mole?
Whispers sloth in curls of smoke
Take a back seat, or play pharaoh
Dance with me and shake your bones
Slow down, it's a science
He's been waiting to bring you down
Snake-eyed, with a sly smile
He can hold you and shake you, child
Leopards laze each on plush pillows
Slender capes of red and chrome
Paperback dreams in their deep doze
Twitch their toes to black mambo
Slow down, it's a science
He's been waiting to bring you down
Snake-eyed, with a sly smile
He can hold you and shake you, child
"Wanna play cheat now?" says the sloth
A domino flush to his nose
Tickle that cheek and take your throne
Pump your veins with gushing gold
Slow down, it's a science
He's been waiting to bring you down
Snake-eyed, with a sly smile
He can hold you and shake you, child
We can hold you